3dcadbrowser.com 2012-09-23

# 3D CAD Browser - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy  
**(Version 1.6 of 31 January 2007)

**What information does** **3D CAD Browser (3Dclub UK)** **collect?**

3D CAD Browser (3Dclub UK) collects some personally identifiable information when you registering on it. We require all users to submit an email address and indicate their billing/mailing address.   
To increase the quality of our services and your user experience, we also collect your browser type, IP address and cookies information. 

**A Special Note about Children**

3D CAD Browser (3Dclub UK) does not gather any personally identifiable information from children that we know is under the age of 13. We believe strongly that parents should play an integral part in their child's on-line experience and should monitor that activity to ensure on-line sites are respecting their child's privacy. 

**Cookies**

3D CAD Browser (3Dclub UK) uses "cookies", or text files sent from our server and saved by your browser to your computer's hard drive. This cookies are sent back only to our server and cannot be read by other web sites' server. Cookies are not programs and cannot be used to read any data or files on your computer. 3D CAD Browser (3Dclub UK) uses cookies to store your navigation information and user preferences.

**Use of Information**

3D CAD Browser (3Dclub UK) collects your contact information and email address to verify your authority to access our system and to contact you when reasonably necessary. 3D CAD Browser (3Dclub UK) may also use any information you have entered into the system as reasonably necessary to administer or provide customer support for the system. 

**Security Measures**

3D CAD Browser (3Dclub UK) employs procedural and technological measures, consistent with legal requirements and the demands of customer service, reasonably designed to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. 

**Policy Changes**

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, 3D CAD Browser (3Dclub UK) may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, 3D CAD Browser (3Dclub UK) will post its updated policy on this page. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.
